OLEKSANDR KODOVBETSKYI

Staines | 07414774366 | oleksandr.kodovbetskyi@gmail.com | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/ak-developer

Professional Summary

I am a final year BCs Computer Science student at Kingston University with experience from various projects that I undertake during my degree and in my spare time. I am focused and driven. I developed great critical thinking and collaboration skills through working in a team. Curiosity for technology keeps me interested in learning new things and pushing myself constantly to achieve more. I would like to further evolve my expertise in software development and implement my knowledge in real-life projects.

Experience

Academic Mentor 09/2022 to Current Kingston University

- Assisting in workshop environments helping second-year students in Programming 2
- Collaborating with a team of lecturers on achieving students' better knowledge in Java and OOP.

Delivery Driver 03/2020 to Current

Amazon Prime

- Successfully completed all deliveries by the time requested.
- Demonstrated my time management skills
- Demonstrated customer service skills.

Barista 03/2020 to 03/2021

Starbucks

- Demonstrating my reliability skills during working under pressure in a busy environment
- · Upselling the menu items
- Demonstrating excellent teamwork during pick hours.

Team member 03/2017 to 02/2020

Sir Christopher Wren Hotel & Spa

- Developed excellent communication and customer service skills
- Was responsible for accurate cash handling and balancing transactions at the end of the day
- Developed planning and time management skills during preparation for the event
- Developed attention to detail while doing the set-ups of the event room.

Technical Skills

- Front end: JS, React, React Native, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Java Swing
- Back-end: Node.js, Express, Java

- Database: MySQL, MongoDB.
- Tools: UNIX Command Line, Git, IntelliJ, VSCODE, Postman, AWS Amplify

Education

BSc (Hons): Computer Science Current

Kingston University
Aiming to obtain 1st grade.

Kingston upon Thames, KTT

Information Technology

07/2020

Kingston College, Kingston College

Kingston-Upon-Thames

Grade: D D

References

References are available on request.

Interests

To express my creativity, I love to discover beautiful nature and cities from a different perspective and always hunt for a better shot. Also, I love playing basketball and feeling the spirit and support of being a part of my team.